This court finds the defendant,
Jolyne Cujoh…
You're an interesting one.
So what did you do?
Why did you get thrown in?
I'm innocent.
…shall be confined to
Green Dolphin Street State Prison
for 15 years.
What is this?
Turns out you have an ability.
"Stone Ocean."
I'll become free
from this ocean of stones.
EPISODE 3: THE VISITOR (1)
Stone Ocean.
When unraveled, this thread can reach far.
However, it becomes less powerful
and inflicts less damage.
When it bundles, it hardens.
Its reach is reduced to about two meters.
Can I break through the bars
with Stone Ocean?
No, it lacked the strength to do so.
The most it could do was this.
My mental energy is harnessed
using the stone inside the charm.
I'd like to get out of here
using this power,
but now's not the time yet.
First, I need to learn
all I can about this place.
Hey, you.
I'm talking to you!
Sorry, but can you lend me some change?
I've got some in my room,
but the call is about to disconnect.
I can pay you back as soon as I'm done.
A dollar is all I need.
I haven't spoken to my family in a while.
Sure.
Here.
Thanks! You saved my skin!
I'll pay you back for sure!
Move, bitch! Don't try to cut in line!
Hold on!
I was waiting for her
to finish for 30 minutes!
I didn't see you waiting in line!
Dumbass, you must be new.
You've got to reserve
these phones in advance.
No one told me that!
Well, now you know.
Also, the reservations
are made a month in advance.
A month?
Why should I wait a whole month
for a few minutes of phone time?
That's what's strange
about prison, isn't it?
Hey, I'll buy that spot
on the phone from you.
And this is the cause of the phenomenon.
Hey, Mom!
I want to call her.
I need to hear her voice.
The voice of my mom…
Jolyne!
How do you fare?
Shut your trap! Keep away from me!
I already told you I'm through with you!
Don't push me away like that.
I'm giving you a warning.
You messed up big time just now.
What?
You just lent a dollar
to that blondie, right?
Get her to pay you back right now.
No, your life here will be over
if you don't get it back now.
What are you saying?
Of course, she'll pay me back.
It was just a dollar.
Hey, you said "just a dollar"!
You're digging your own grave
with that mentality!
What?
Listen closely, Jolyne.
At the Aquarium,
lending or borrowing money between inmates
is one thing
you should avoid at all costs.
Even if it's just a dollar.
Let's say that you fail
to get the dollar back.
You know what will happen?
You'll become a bottom feeder like her.
"Jolyne the newbie
couldn't even extort back her dollar."
The rumor will spread like wildfire
and you'll be the target in no time.
Just like her.
One after another, every single day.
Once you're out of money, you'll be forced
to give your body and even your mind.
Isn't that what hell on earth is like?
Hey, now. You're exaggerating.
Am I, now? It was
"just a dollar" for her at first.
See that blonde from earlier?
She went to her room,
but she's not planning on
coming down for you.
I'm telling you for your own sake.
Got a minute?
Oh, hello there.
Apparently, this one's a classic.
Have you read it?
No.
I'm here for the money.
Are you ready to pay me back?
Oh, of course.
A dollar, right? I haven't forgotten.
It's all in my head, don't worry about it.
I'll pay you back later.
You said you have the money in your room.
You went back, right?
Do you have it now?
Shut up, you bitch!
I said I'll give it back later.
I don't have it now, you hear me?
You a tightwad or what?
Anyway, can you lend me ten more?
I can call up friends on the outside
and ask for more money!
Please? You've got to have some on you.
Come on, don't be shy!
What's this…
What the heck is this?
I can't hold it in!
Hey, you in there!
Can you hurry it up?
I know you're in there!
I'll give you the dollar!
-Please!
-You'll pay me later, right?
Don't worry about it. Take your time.
I'll buy the time from you!
I'll pay five… No, ten dollars!
Sold!
Sorry. That'll be ten dollars.
Hey, you.
Go use the bathroom next.
Someone else will have
the urge to use it soon.
It's up to you whether you can get
your money back, though.
You're the only one who can save yourself.
What the… What's going on?
That's right, I'll be leaving soon.
Somehow, I'll get out.
Inmate number FE40536.
I'm returning to my cell.
Please unlock this door.
Tomorrow at noon,
you will have a visitor.
But you must not meet him.
You must not go to the visitation room.
If you do,
you and others will be in grave danger.
A fate more terrible than death
will happen.
Who was that just now?
How did a child sneak in here?
Hey you!
Didn't you hear my order to standby?
Do not touch the bars!
Stand back!
Open the door.
Right now!
I said do not grab the bars!
A visitor is coming tomorrow at noon.
Not to see you, though,
but someone in the next building,
you know what I mean?
That's the intel.
Oh, by the way,
you got it on backwards.
Your pants, I mean.
You're overreacting.
Sorry about yesterday, FE40536.
But it's your fault
for grabbing onto the bars like that.
Rules are rules.
I had already let go.
But you still hit me twice.
What? Did you mutter something?
Couldn't hear you.
Never mind. How can I help you?
Someone's here to see you.
Stand up. I'll handcuff you.
A visitor? Who is it, my mom?
How the hell should I know?
Give me your hands.
Stand on the mark right there.
I'll explain the rules.
You have 30 minutes.
You are allowed to hold hands,
but kissing or undressing are not allowed.
You will receive anything
they bring after the visitation.
Foreign languages are forbidden.
Depending on the visit,
the guard may choose to end it.
Wait there until you're authorized.
You mustn't go any further.
Turn around. Go back to your room!
It's not too late!
Who are you?
How did a child like you get in here?
I don't quite understand either,
but there are some things
more fearsome than death.
And it's happening at this very prison.
So please turn back. Go back to your cell!
No. My mom must be here to see me.
I want to see her.
She must be missing me too.
I need to let her know
that I'm doing well!
Then take this.
It should protect you.
FE40536, all right.
Enter!
These are bones!
Stop dawdling. Get in.
Jolyne, did you receive the charm
I asked your mom to give you?
Dad…
STAND NAME: STAR PLATINUM
STAND MASTER: JOTARO KUJO
Car and wallet theft. Assault.
This must be some mistake!
My Jolyne would never…
Since she's only 14,
she won't be charged this time.
You're headed to Tokyo?
This is your daughter we're talking about!
Why not go tomorrow instead?
And you call yourself her father?
Hello? Are you there?
Jolyne, are you listening?
Where's the pendant?
I'd rather receive disciplinary action.
Had I known it was you,
I wouldn't have come here.
Hey, open the door!
Shit, I hit him too hard.
Get up!
Good grief.
Jolyne, listen up.
It was not your boyfriend Romeo
who conspired to frame you for murder
and had you sent to this prison.
Johngalli A.
This man is incarcerated
in the men's prison here.
He's ex-military.
A veteran sniper who could hit his mark
under any difficult circumstance.
According to the report,
his vision has deteriorated
due to cataracts.
This man was behind it all.
Even that manslaughter accident.
A henchman of Johngalli A.
kidnapped an innocent hitchhiker
and threw him in front of the car.
He also hired a greedy lawyer
to set up the trust-fund baby.
Johngalli A. was pulling the strings
from this prison.
Help me, Jolyne!
Do you know what a "plea deal" is?
I love you!
This court finds the defendant,
-Jolyne Cujoh…
-Fifteen years…
Damn you! You hit me twice yesterday!
Dammit!
What's the point?
Why would he plot my imprisonment?
-Sit.
-Answer me!
I said sit.
Listen. Johngalli A.'s target
was you all along.
It's so that he can eliminate you
any time he wishes
within these prison walls.
Why is he after me?
Because you are my daughter.
You are of the Joestar bloodline.
Joestar?
The Joestar bloodline
can be traced back hundreds of decades.
And Johngalli A. plots to
take revenge on our family.
We are endowed with
the wonderful gift to move others.
But at times,
powerful emotions leave dregs.
Dregs called grudges, that is.
In the past,
I defeated a mortal enemy
of the Joestar clan.
Johngalli A. is a pawn of this enemy.
We've never met,
but I have no doubt about it.
Though it's been over 20 years,
Johngalli A. uses his fanaticism
for this man to exact his revenge.
I don't understand. I thought
you were just a marine biologist.
What's this about enemies and grudges?
Just know that you are being targeted.
I'll get you out immediately.
We will bypass the law.
Have you acquired your Stand yet?
"Stand"?
As my daughter, you are predisposed
to the ability to use this power.
Did you see any changes
from the pendant I gave you?
It seems you have.
That's the Stand ability.
Stand… Then you too?
Use your power to get out.
Okay?
Quit your yapping.
Don't try to act like a father now.
So you're finally here to save me.
What, because you love me?
I've already forgotten about you.
But fine, whatever.
I'll keep that shocking story
and the Stand ability in mind.
You can go now.
Don't ever visit me again.
My handcuffs!
When did I get out of them?
Since when…
The brand is different.
The guard didn't even approach the table.
Jolyne, get away from that door!
Star Platinum: The World!
Time, stop!
What happened just now?
Stay still! The fight has already begun.
What's the layout to the right?
Any windows in that direction?
Two or three. But they're all barred.
This is a real bullet.
This bullet, called a Sniper Premium,
is specific to rifles.
The shot was undoubtedly
taken by Johngalli A.
Hold on, I thought he was an inmate.
Inmates are prohibited
from even having pens.
Is that so?
But guns can be disassembled, you see.
Precise parts may be snuck in
through various objects.
Guards can be bribed by his henchmen
and the objects won't get searched.
Little by little, slowly but surely.
But we're in the women's prison!
He can't possibly shoot me from the men's!
We're inside a building.
There are obstructions!
A rifle and an ability make that possible.
In other words, Johngalli A. is,
without a doubt, a Stand user.
Look.
What's that?
Keep your distance.
Certainly, that's not just some rubbish.
But it's moving away.
It seems really light.
It's just floating in the air.
Don't engage it.
First, we must know what it can do.
It dodged!
I said don't engage it.
Can it see my thread?
Don't be so loud.
It's reacting to something.
However, not to the thread.
Its movement seems unrelated
to the thread.
Oh, could it be reacting to that?
What was it called?
The change in the air from the thread.
Like, the movement of the air?
Aerodynamics.
It detected our positions
using aerodynamics.
All right, so he knows our location.
But how can he shoot us
from the men's dormitory?
That's the real problem.
Jolyne, you were saved
by a fortuitous accident.
Do not make a move
until we understand the contraption.
Don't order me around!
-I know that!
-You… FE40536!
You're done for, I'll have you know!
Got it? Jolyne Cujoh!
-What?
-It's headed towards us!
I'll make sure you get disciplined!
Don't move!
After I beat you to death, that is!
Calm down!
Jolyne, don't leave the wall!
I know! And don't order me!
Let's knock him out
before we get into more trouble!
Damn you, who do you think
you're talking to?
You bastard!
Jolyne!
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter